[Music]
Indian government's leading insurance
company, ICICI Lombard, has
launched a health insurance scheme called Elevate, based on artificial intelligence.
Through this revolutionary scheme, ICICI
Lombard has become the first company in the country to offer
its
customers the flexibility to design a plan tailored to their needs.
Vivek Srivastava, head of health agency at ICICI Lombard, provided details
about the scheme at a media conference.
He later spoke to HDTV.
ICICI Lombard has
launched a new health insurance plan for its customers.
This product is called Elevate.
Elevate is the first
product in the country that offers its customers numerous specialties,
numerous advantages, and numerous features.
We have incorporated many features into this product. The first and foremost
importance of this product, if you understand it, is its
complete personalization for the customer. You can customize the
product according to the customer's needs.
This product can be made as per the requirement of the customer.
If the customer needs any feature,
it can be added to it and if any feature is
not needed, it can be removed.
More importantly, if you see,
we have given many such features in it
which are not available in the industry, like there is an
add-on called Infa Care, after taking which the
customer can be completely rest assured about his claim.
Under this feature, you can make
any claim in your lifetime, no matter what amount the
customer has taken. Infa
amount means there is no limit on it.
Suppose someone has taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh
and if he has taken this add-on feature, then if a claim of Rs 1
crore, Rs 2 crore, Rs 5 crore,
etc. comes in his lifetime, the
company will pay it. This feature, this benefit is
not available in any other product in the country till date. Secondly,
for the bonus in it, we have given a feature called Power Booster,
which says that the
sum insured of the customer, for whomever he has
bought the policy, whether  Whether there is a claim or
not, every year his sum assured will
increase by 100% and it will increase by 100%
till he keeps renewing the policy.
That means today if someone has
bought a policy of Rs 10 lakh and he has availed
this feature, after 10 years every year
we will increase that Rs 10 lakh by another Rs 10 lakh.
After 10 years that Rs 10 lakh will automatically
convert into a crore. Similarly,
we have given another feature which is again unique and is being
known in the industry,
people are accepting it and this is
one of the best feature of the industry and that is Jump
Start. Here, if any of you customers has any
pre-existing disease or any
disease already and he declares it to us
and takes this feature, then we will cover the cost of that
disease for him. The normal waiting period
in any policy, like in this policy it is 3
years, we will reduce that waiting period to
30 days from 31 days in this policy.
Coverage will also be extended to that disease. These are
some unique features that have been
introduced for the first time in our policy. Another feature in this is the
sum insurance feature. We have provided customers with the facility to choose sum insurance.
It starts from Rs 5 lakh and this is the highest
level. Today, plans of up to Rs 1
crore, 2 crore and 6 crore are available in the market.
In this product, we have
given customers the option of unlimited sum insurance so that
they can choose unlimited sum insurance,
which gives them complete freedom of all these features.
This is the first such product which is AI
driven. In this, we also recommend the best features to the customers based on their
area, their earnings, their family size.
So, this is a
unique product in itself. It is the first product
in the market. And I think the response
we have received in the first few days is
amazing. Seeing the interest of the people, we are also
excited and we know
that this product is going to do very well for us.
So, thank you for attending this
and more.
Importantly, you all will be happy to know
that this product is available
through all the channel partners under ICC Lumbard and
through the website. Thank you very much and
thank you because this product is
Artificial Intelligence based. So, does the
customer also have to be smart
for this? Look, the customer is already smart. The
customer
thinks a lot of things in his own mind, but
what is going to happen through Artificial Intelligence is that we are at least
telling him that your
requirement should be at least this, but
again, as I said, it is personalized in nature, it is
customizable. Whatever we are telling the
customer, two more things can be added to it,
two more things can be removed.
Again, it is a freedom of the customer to choose
what he wants to buy and what not to buy. So, at the
time of insuring, the
customer will feed these details or someone will assist him.
So, if any customer is
buying this product through any advisor, he does
not have to do anything, he just has to tell his advisor his details.
And the details are also basic details, I don't know
how many people you want to insure,
if there are four members in the family, then
what are the birth dates of those four, what are their phone numbers,
your basic details, what area do you
live in, after taking this, let me
tell you the basic premium and what coverage we can offer for it,
give me an example of a typical premium, so the
range of premium is very diverse
because it starts from 5 lakhs and goes up
to unlimited, it starts from 18 years to
unlimited, meaning you can choose people of any age group, so the
range is very
big, but just I want to give this example,
when you add the same features
and some of the features which I said are
first in the industry,
in the industry,
with the brand of ICC Labad, with the service we provide
and the features we are providing, it will
probably be the most attractive in the market,
I just want to say this, thank you, thank you,
Madina School, best academic faculty,
excellent discipline, where both education and
upbringing are 100 percent first continuously for 43 years
Unparalleled
record of class and distinction results Unparalleled achievements in sports too Keeping up with the
pace and demands of time, we have
Hung Science Computer and Robotics Labs and
that too in affordable fee structure
For admissions contact
4145 or 6304
8143 Himayat Nagar for Boys and Girls
Nampally For Girls and Boys up to Fifth
Standard Medina Schools Himayat Nagar and
Nampally Hyderabad
[Music]